<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>topic/platform-engineering on Shaishav Kumar</title>
    <link>https://blog.shaishav.kr/tags/topic/platform-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in topic/platform-engineering on Shaishav Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://blog.shaishav.kr/tags/topic/platform-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AsyncAwait Organizations</title>
      <link>https://blog.shaishav.kr/pages/asyncawait-organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 22:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.shaishav.kr/pages/asyncawait-organizations/</guid>
      <description>AsyncAwait Organizations Illustrate the problem Talk about the Core Idea of the Solution Evidence about the Solution Approach Solution Playbook Call to Action Footnotes Decision Framework
Is it easy to explain the solution? Is it easy to roll out? within a team? can be adopted by a mid-senior member in their 20% time in one sprint Across Teams? Across the whole org? Is it easy to enforce adoption? eg. Linting style guides using Vale for a Docs repository, or GitHub actions for release tags names.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Git Workflow with Stacked PRs</title>
      <link>https://blog.shaishav.kr/pages/efficient-git-workflow-with-stacked-prs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 22:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.shaishav.kr/pages/efficient-git-workflow-with-stacked-prs/</guid>
      <description>Efficient Git Workflow with Stacked PRs Illustrate the problem Big PRs %% statistics about time spent by senior devs in PR reviews. short 2-3lines. quote with reference+statistics from mid sized startups %% %% why big PRs are harder to make sense of . general intro - 2 lines. %% %% define BIG PR. 400line changes as per google&amp;rsquo;s guidelines. short , 2 lines %% %% types of PR changes. chore vs feature, vs hotfix vs bugfix vs improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rise of Internal Developer Portals (iDp) - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://blog.shaishav.kr/pages/rise-of-internal-developer-portals-idp-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 22:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.shaishav.kr/pages/rise-of-internal-developer-portals-idp-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Rise of Internal Developer Portals (iDp) - Part 1 Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s rapidly evolving software development landscape, staying ahead of the curve is crucial for success. One emerging trend that has gained significant traction is the adoption of Internal Developer Portals (iDp).
In this introductory blog post, we will explore the concept of iDp, its growing popularity in 2023, and why it is essential for modern software development.
Whether you are a startup founder, a cloud-native enthusiast, or a Kubernetes aficionado, this blog series will provide you with practical insights to leverage the power of internal developer portals and maximize your team&amp;rsquo;s productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
